Josh Gottheil Collection ARC.0150
Library and Archives
- Dead Relatives and Better Youth Organization, 1985-1986
  - Cover artwork for tape cassette recording of live performance at "Jam for Life," a benefit for Local AIDS programs, at Mabel's, 1985 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 36-37)
  - Poster for "A Jam for Life" with The Outnumbered, Nitelife, The Models, Weird Summer, Farmboys, ¡Ack-Ack!, Otis and the Elevators, Dead Relatives, and Eclectrics, 1985 December 8 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 5)
  - Newspaper clipping featuring Deni Girard (The Motels), "Jam for Life." The Daily Illini, 1985 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 38)
  - Block, Jill. "12-hour 'Jam for Life' raises estimated $1,000 for AIDS." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette, 1985 December 9 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 39)
  - "Editorial: AIDS Concert." The Daily Illini, 1985 December 12 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 40)
  - Paaswell, George. "A Jam for Life." The Daily Illini Arts and Entertainment Directory, 1985 December 13-19 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 51)
  - Flyer for Penguin Dust, plus Didjits, Dead Relatives, Red Pajamas, and Just Plain Macarthur, Illini Union Room C (Better Youth Organization presentation), 1985 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 41-42)
  - Ticket for a Benefit Concert, sponsored by Students for World Improvement and the Better Youth Organization at Illini Union, Room C, 1985 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 43)
  - Receipts for purchases of Dead Relatives cassette tapes, 1985 December 31-1986 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 44-51)
  - 45 rpm record picture sleeve for Automon's "Emily's House" / "Don't Frustrate Ronnie", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 52)
  - Album flat for Hüsker Dü, Flip Your Wig, 1985 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 74)
  - Daily Illini New Student Edition 1985 article on Dead Relatives and Champaign, Illinois rock scene. (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 52)
  - Dead Relatives audio cassette tape cover art, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 53)
  - "Four views of C-U's music scene, no bullshit." The Daily Illini New Student Edition (2 pages), 1985 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 53)
  - Poster for Dig This: A Tribute to the Great Strike, 1985 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 80)
  - Poster for Minutemen Project: Mersh, 1985 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 81)
  - Mabel's "Musician's Register" and flyers, 1985-1988 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 6-59)
  - Flyer for the Dead Relatives, circa 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 54)
  - Advertisement for purchase of Dead Relatives audiocassette tapes at Record Swap or mail order, circa 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 55-56)
  - Flyer for Dead Relatives on WEFT 90.1 FM, 1986 February 3 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 57-58)
  - Flyer for Descendents, I Don't Want to Grow Up, and Dead Relatives at Illini Union Room C (Better Youth Organization production), 1986 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 59)
  - Poster for Descendents and the Dead Relatives, Illini Union Room C, 1986 February 10 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 17)
  - Ticket for Descendents and Dead Relatives at Illini Union Room C (Better Youth Organization production), 1986 February 10 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 60)
  - Poster for Toxic Reasons with the Dead Relatives at Thornburn Center, 1986 March 14 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 60)
  - Poster for Dead Relatives and Farm Boys at Mabel's, 1986 March 31 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 61)
  - Flyer for Toxic Reasons with the Dead Relatives at Thornburn Center, 1986 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 61-63)
  - Student Organization Resource Fee Board application for funding, circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 64)
  - Ticket for Toxic Reasons and Dead Relatives at Thornburn Center (handwritten notes on back) (Better Youth Organization/Subversive Sounds/WPGU production), 1986 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 65)
  - Flyer for Glorious Din with the Dead Relatives at Trito's Uptown, 1986 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 66)
  - Poster for Glorious Din, Leading Stolen Horses, with the Dead Relatives at Trito's Uptown, 1986 April 15 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 18)
  - Program for Glorious Din with the Dead Relatives at Trito's Uptown, 1986 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 67)
  - Flyer for Band Jam on the Quad (Better Youth Organization production), 1986 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 8, Object 68-69)
  - Poster for Generic Air, McWilson, Ill-Noize, Alien Nation, Cries and Whispers, Free Loaders, Blood Brain Barrier, Pink Green Days, Dead Relatives at University of Illinois Quad, 1986 May 10 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 19)
- Musician's Register, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Press kits, press releases, and mailings, 1985-1987
  - 1985-1987
    - Blank flyer for Rebels and Infidels, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 1)
    - Tour schedule for Black Flag "Loose Nut", 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 2-3)
    - Blank flyer for Capitol Punishment, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 4-5)
    - Press kit for Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 6-10)
    - Press kit for Tension, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 11)
    - Subterranean Records mail order form, 1986 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 12-13)
    - Press kit for Disinfect, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 14)
    - Press kit for Drivin' and Cryin', 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 15-17)
    - Promotional poster for Rhythm Pigs, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 18)
    - Press kit for 7Seconds (Better Youth Organization), circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 19)
    - Press kit for 11:55, circa 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 20)
    - Press kit for Carnival Season, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 21)
    - Press kit for The Connells, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 22-24)
    - Press kit for Dash Rip Rock from 688 Records, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 25)
    - Press kit for dB's from International Record Syndicate, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 26-27)
    - Press kit for Enigma Records, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 28)
    - Press kit for Fetchin' Bones, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 29)
    - Press kit for The Fluid, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 30-32)
    - Press kit for Bulging Eye Booking and Management, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 33)
    - Press kit for Royal Crescent Mob, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 34-36)
    - Press kit for Scratch Acid, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 37)
    - Press kit for Suburban Death Trip, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 38)
    - Press kit for Ben Vaughn, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10, Object 39-41)
  - 1988
    - Correspondence from Capitol Records regarding Lloyd Cole and The Commotions, 1988 September 12 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 1)
    - Triad Artists, Inc. Talent and Literary Agency promotional materials, 1988 October 7 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 2)
    - Press kit for Alice Donut, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 3)
    - Press kit for Apathy, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 4)
    - Press kit for Defenestration from Bulging Eye Booking and Management, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 5)
    - Press kit for Enigma, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 6-7)
    - Press kit for Jump the Wall, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 8)
    - Press kit for Lazy Cowgirls, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 9)
    - Press kit for Let's Active from International Record Syndicate, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 10)
    - Press kit for Low Meato from Bulging Eye Booking, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 11)
    - Press kit for Mudhoney, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 12-14)
    - Pixies fax and promotional photographs, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 15)
    - Sonic Youth press release, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 16)
    - Soul Asylum promotional flyer for Hang Time, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 17)
    - Souled American correspondence and press kit, 1988 September 26 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 18)
    - Touch and Go press release for Arsenal's Manipulator, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 19)
    - Press kit for Velvet Elvis, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11, Object 20)
  - Flaming Lips, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Jonathan Richman and the Modern Lovers, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Timbuk 3, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1989, undated
    - Monterey Peninsula Artists list, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 1)
    - Promotional photograph for Breathless from Rough Trade, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 2)
    - Correspondence to Gottheil from Michele, Bulging Eye Booking and Promotion, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 3)
    - Press kit for Dayglow Abortions, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 4)
    - Descendents fan club mailing, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 5)
    - Promotional photograph for Jerry Dale McFadden from Bulging Eye Booking, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 6)
    - Promotional photograph for Meat Puppets from SST, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 7)
    - Press kit for Membranes from Homestead Records, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 8)
    - Correspondence to Morrissey and Johnny Marr Fans from Bruce McGuire, King of the Replacements in '89 Fan Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 9)
    - Press kit for My Dad Is Dead, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 10)
    - Promotional photograph for Pedal Jets, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 11)
    - Promotional photograph for Rapeman from Touch and Go Records, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 12)
    - Press kit for Raw Power, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 13)
    - Sugar Cubes promotional flyer, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 14)
    - Press kit for They Might Be Giants, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 15-21)
    - Vandals promotional photograph from Restless Records, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 22)
    - Venture Bookings list, undated (Box 1, Folder 15, Object 23)
- No More Censorship Defense Fund, 1986-1987
  - No More Censorship Defense Fund press kit, 1986 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 1-2)
  - Correspondence from Billy and Becca, Better Youth Organization to Subversive Sounds, 1987 January 13 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 3)
  - Flyer for No More Censorship Defense Fund concert with the Didjits, the Outnumbered, and Buckethead at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 4)
  - Correspondence from Dirk B.G. Dirksen, Volunteer Executive Producer, No More Censorship Defense Fund, to Josh Gottheil and Jon Ginoli, 1987 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 5)
  - Mailing from No More Censorship Defense Fund, [1987?] March 12 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 6-7)
  - Mailing from No More Censorship Defense Fund, 1987 July 30 (Box 1, Folder 16, Object 8)
- Subversive Sounds Productions, 1986-1988
  - Subversive Sounds Productions press release - schedule, Summer 1986 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 62)
  - Flyer with Subversive Sounds Productions schedule, 1986 Summer/Fall (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 1)
  - Flyer for Watts Baldhead, HSR, and Ill-Noize at the Channing Murray Foundation, 1986 June 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 2)
  - Flyer for Watts Baldhead, HSR, and Ill-Noize; flyer for 1096 and Charming Deviants at 1007 East University Avenue on reverse, 1986 June 8, 1986 June 28 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 3)
  - Flyer for Das Damen at Club Red; Rhythm Pigs flyer on reverse, 1986 June 29, 1986 July 1 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 4)
  - Alternative Tentacles Records mailing, 1986 July 14 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 5)
  - Flyer for Doggy Style with Ratt, 1986 July 17 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 6)
  - Poster for Doggy Style, with McWillson, at 10 Shitty Guys, 1986 July 17 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 63-64)
  - Poster for Royal Crescent Mob with the Bowery Boys at Trito's Uptown, 1986 July 27 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 65)
  - Poster for SNFU, Shudder to Think, and Dead KCIS at Latzer Hall-YMCA, 1986 July 28 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 20)
  - Flyer for Beefeater, with the Didjits and H.S.R. at Illini Union, 1986 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 7)
  - Flyer for Life Sentence, Grey March, and the Outbreaks at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 August 22 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 8-9)
  - Photocopied article on Josh Gottheil, Subversive Sounds, and performances at the Channing-Murray Foundation, The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1986 August 22 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 10)
  - Flyer for M.D.C., Cheetah Crome Motherfuckers, and Dead Relatives at the Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 11-12)
  - Poster for M.D.C., Cheetahcrome Motherfuckers, and Dead Relatives at the Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 September 7 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 21)
  - Ticket for M.D.C., Cheetah Crome Motherfuckers, and Dead Relatives at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 September 7 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 13)
  - Flyer for Die Kreuzen, with Defoliants and Cries and Whispers (3 designs), 1986 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 14-16)
  - Poster for Die Kreuzen with the Defoliants, Cries and Whispers, at Illini Union Room C, 1986 September 18 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 66)
  - Poster for Capitol Punishment plus Random Noise at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 9 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 22)
  - Flyer for Subversive Sounds Productions and Record Swap, 1986 October 9-1986 December 13 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 17a)
  - Bouvier, Pierre, et al. "C-U Around." The Daily Illini, circa 1986 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 17b)
  - Card advertisement for Big Black, with Urge Overkill, Didjits, ClubCrack at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 18)
  - Poster for Big Black, Urge Overkill, the Didjits, and Club Crack at the Channing Murray Foundation, 1986 October 19 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 23)
  - Table card for Big Black, with Urge Overkill, the Didjits, ClubCrack at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 19)
  - Ticket for Big Black, Urge Overkill, The Didjits, and Club Crack at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 20)
  - Dey, Jim. "Campus curfew arrests continue." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1986 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 21)
  - Crane, Mandy. "Thrash on eve of destruction." The Daily Illini, 1986 October 21 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 54)
  - Poster for Adolescents, Scab at the Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 22 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 24)
  - Ticket for Adolescents, with Scab and U.P.S. at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 22)
  - Flyer for Raw Power, with Dayglow Abortions and Problem Children at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 23)
  - Poster for Raw Power with Dayglow Abortions and Problem Children at Channing Murray Foundation, 1986 November 6 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 67)
  - Ticket for Raw Power, with Dayglow Abortions and Problem Children at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 November 6 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 24)
  - Flyer for 7 Seconds with Verbal Assault, 1986 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 25-27)
  - Ticket for 7 Seconds at the Channing-Murray Foundation, 1986 December 14 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 28)
  - Block, Jill. "The Power of Punk." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1986 December 19 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 3)
  - Black-and-white photograph of Gottheil at the Channing Murray Foundation, taken by the Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette, circa 1986 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 29)
  - Poster for 7 Seconds EP Walk Together Rock Together, 1986 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 83)
  - Poster for Robyn Hitchcock and the Egyptians Element of Light, 1986 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 82)
  - Poster for Snake Corps' Victory Parade with "Always Be the Same" and "Painted Ocean", 1986 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 68)
  - Royalty, Doug. "1986: Some chips off the old rock." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1987 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 30)
  - Crane, Mandy. "Local rockers contribute to Biafra's defense." The Daily Illini [photocopy], 1987 February 5 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 25)
  - "What's Up" page from The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend with Toxic Reasons advertisement, 1987 February 13 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 4)
  - Bouvier, Pierre and Jay Wilkins, compilers. "Cultural enrichment aplenty this week." The Daily Illini Directory, 1987, February 13-19 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 31)
  - Flyer for Toxic Reasons, with Sloppy Seconds and Transgression, 1987 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 32-34)
  - Poster for Toxic Reasons, Sloppy Seconds, Transgression at Urbana Thornburn Center, 1987 February 14 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 26)
  - Ticket for Toxic Reasons, with Sloppy Seconds and Transgression, 1987 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 35)
  - Flyer for the Urge Overkill with Didjits and Shakes at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 36)
  - Flyer for Subversive Sounds Productions, 1987 March 26-1987 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 37)
  - Newspaper clipping of Flaming Lips photo, The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1987 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 38)
  - Page from The Daily Illini Directory with Flaming Lips article and album review, 1987 April 17-23 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 55)
  - Flyer for The Flaming Lips plus Tugrik Dhugugrik, 1987 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 39)
  - Ticket for The Flaming Lips plus special guests at Chins, 1987 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 40)
  - Flyer for Scratch Acid at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 41)
  - Ticket for Scratch Acid with Th' Inbred at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 42)
  - Newspaper clipping of Mojo Nixon photo, The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette, 1987 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 43)
  - Flyer for Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper with Lonely Trailer at Trito's Uptown, 1987 April 26 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 44)
  - Poster for Big Black, Didjits at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 May 3 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 69)
  - Ticket for Big Black, plus Didjits, at Channing-Murray Foundation, 1987 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 45)
  - Flyer for the Flaming Lips, plus Weird Summer, at Trito's Uptown, 1987 September 1 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 46-47)
  - "This Week." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1988 April 29 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 5)
  - Poster for Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper, with the Farmers, at Mabel's, 1988 May 5 (Box-folder OS1-1, Object 70)
  - Poster for Pixies with Schoolyard Truce at Mabel's, 1988 June 1 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 27)
  - Ticket for Pixies at Mabel's, 1988 June 1 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 48)
  - Press release from Subversive Sounds Productions, 1988 August 8 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 49)
  - Flyer for Dough Boys, with Titanic Love Affair at Trito's Uptown, 1988 August 10 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 50)
  - Flyer for Subversive Sounds Productions, 1988 September 7-November 1 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 51)
  - Ticket for Chalice at Mabel's, September 12 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 52)
  - Flyer for Living Colour, 1988 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 53-54)
  - Letterhead for Subversive Sounds Productions, undated (Box 1, Folder 17, Object 55-56)
- Flyer mockups, 1986-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  General note
  In some cases, the final copy of the mockup is also available here.
- KALX 90.7 FM, 1986-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Newspapers on the Champaign-Urbana music scene, 1986-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Band contact information and calendar [RESTRICTED], 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Access Restrictions
  This file is confidential and is, therefore, RESTRICTED. Consult the Library and Archives staff in advance of your visit to ensure access to these materials is available.
- Expenses, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Fanzines from Champaign-Urbana, 1986-1988, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Titles include Starcourse, Better Than No Thing, Mangozine, and No Cover.
- Subversive Sounds mailing list [RESTRICTED], circa 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Notebook of "The Josh Sessions", 1987 April 5-1988 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Playlists for WEFT 90.1 FM, 1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Anthony Poulis and Subversive Sounds Productions, 1987-1988, undated
  - Flyer for the Meat Puppets, 1987 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 1)
  - Ticket for Meat Puppets, plus Nice Strong Arm, at Mabel's, 1987 August 30 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 2)
  - Ticket for dB's, with Dash Rip Rock, at Mabel's, 1987 September 21 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 3)
  - 1987 October 14 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 56)
  - Card advertisement for Throwing Muses at Mabel's, 1987 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 4)
  - Ticket for Throwing Muses, with special guests, at Mabel's, 1987 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 5)
  - Artemakis, Angelo. "Mabel's to host avant-garde 10,000 Maniacs.", circa 1987 October 14 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 6)
  - Poster for 10,000 Maniacs, plus the Connells, at Mabel's, 1987 October 29 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 28)
  - Ticket for 10,000 Maniacs at Mabel's, 1987 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 7)
  - Flyer for Camper Van Beethoven, plus guests Souled Americans, at Mabel's, 1987 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 8)
  - Ticket for Camper Van Beethoven at Mabel's, 1987 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 9)
  - Flyer for Hüsker Dü plus special guests at Mabels, 1987 December 8 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 10)
  - Color photograph of Gottheil with Kim Deal, Pixies, in San Francisco, 1988 February (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 11)
  - Ticket for dB's, with Fetchin' Bones and Schoolyard Truce, at Mabel's, 1988 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 12)
  - Flyer for Subversive Sounds Productions & Anthony Poulos, 1988 April 14-1988 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 13)
  - Flyer for They Might Be Giants at Mabel's, 1988 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 14)
  - Ticket for They Might Be Giants at Mabel's, 1988 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 15)
  - Poster for The Flaming Lips at Mabel's, 1988 April 24 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 29)
  - Poster for the Flaming Lips, Didjits, and Shakes at Mabel's, 1988 April 24 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 30)
  - Ticket for the Flaming Lips at Mabel's, 1988 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 16)
  - Kamienski, Laura Ann and Syd Slobodnick, compilers. "Elvis is everywhere, even Mabel's." The Daily Illini, 1988 April 29-May 5 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 57)
  - Advertisement for Billy Bragg/Michelle Shocked performance at Mabel's, The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1988 April 29 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 6)
  - Eirinberg, Scott. "Bragg to charm and challenge." The Daily Illini, 1988 May 4 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 58)
  - Poet, J. "Billy Bragg: Back from the USSR." In These Times, 21, 1988 May 4-1988 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 17)
  - Ticket for Billy Bragg at Mabel's, 1988 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 18)
  - Flyer for Billy Bragg, with Michelle Shocked, and Mojo Nixon, with Skid Roper and The Farmers, Mabel's, 1988 May 4-1988 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 19)
  - Zine pages with information on Billy Bragg, with Michelle Shocked at Mabel's, circa 1988 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 20)
  - Ticket for Mojo Nixon and Skid Roper at Mabel's, 1988 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 21)
  - Springer, P. Gregory. "Lost in America." The Champaign-Urbana News-Gazette Weekend, 1988 May 6 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 7)
  - Gaffigan, Michelle. "Just bo-day-shus! Roper and Nixon share wisdom of life." The Daily Illini, 1988 May 9 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 59)
  - Flyer for My Dad Is Dead, plus Membranes, at Trito's Uptown, 1988 July 31 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 22)
  - Ticket for Living Colour at Mabel's, 1988 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 23)
  - Bernard, Dan. "Living Colour delivers thrashing, funky good time." The Daily Illini, 1988 September 20 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 60)
  - Poster for Soul Asylum with Titanic Love Affair at Mabel's, 1988 September 22 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 31)
  - Ticket for Soul Asylum at Mabel's, 1988 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 24)
  - Reflex Magazine, 1:7, 1988 September (Box 1, Folder 27, Object 25)
  - Poster for Royal Crescent Mob with 16 Tons at Chin's, 1988 October 30 (Box-folder OS1-2, Object 32)